<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sochi Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="parks">Parks</string>
    <string name="museums">Museums and Sights</string>
    <string name="restaurants">Restaurants and Cafe</string>
    <string name="nature">Nature attractions</string>
    <string name="entertainments">Entertainments</string>

    <!-- Strings for Parks -->

    <string name="parks_riviera">Riviera Park of Culture and Leisure</string>
    <string name="parks_riviera_description">
        Play games and take part in amusement rides at Riviera Park of Culture and Leisure, one of the city\'s most popular parks.
        This site combines a number of features for visitors, including art galleries, carnival rides, an old-fashioned Ferris wheel,
        and an aquarium with a live dolphin show. The park is also home to Soviet structures and magnolia trees planted by Russian
        astronauts and dedicated to peaceful space exploration.
        Put Riviera Park of Culture and Leisure into our Sochi trip itinerary maker app to see other points of interest to visit
        during your vacation in Sochi.
    </string>

    <string name="parks_southern_cultures">Southern Cultures Park</string>
    <string name="parks_southern_cultures_description">
        The park was planted in 1911, on the lands of General Daniil Drachevsky,
        at his Sluchainoe estate, by the landscape architect Arnold Regel and gardner Roman Skrivanik.
        Using 11 hectares of land, they had created the park-and-garden ensemble with a system of ponds.
        Almost twenty years later, the park was given its contemporary name and greatly expanded.
        Since then, it has changed a lot, adding new wooden sculptures and plants, and remaining a favourite attraction for the local
        residents and resort visitors.\nSouthern Cultures Park captivates visitors with its combination of wide alleys,
        intersected by numerous paths and roads that can alternatively take you to the thicket of coniferous trees,
        or to some sweeping meadows, to exotic palmtrees and pampas grass, or eucalyptus groves.
        In the park’s heartland lie the large ponds with islets and bridges.
   </string>

    <string name="parks_olimpiyskiy">Olimpic Park</string>
    <string name="parks_olimpiyskiy_description">
        Sochi Olympic Park is an Olympic Park that was constructed for the 2014 Winter Olympics and 2014 Winter Paralympics.
        The Olympic Park houses the main Olympic Stadium used for the Games\' ceremonies, and the venues that were used for indoor sports
        such as hockey, figure skating, curling, and speed skating.
        It also houses training facilities, the Olympic Village, the international broadcasting centre, and other amenities.
        The park was designed so that all of the venues would be accessible within walking distance of each other.
        The venues are situated around a water basin containing a fountain known as "The Waters of the Olympic Park";
        designed by California-based WET (which also designed the cauldron for the 2002 Winter Olympics in Salt Lake City),
        the fountain measures 5.3 meters in diameter with a capacity of about 700,000 gallons of water, featuring more than 250 nozzles
        and jet systems that can create fog and choreographed water displays set to music.
    </string>

    <string name="parks_dendrariy">Arboretum Botanical Garden Dendrariy</string>
    <string name="parks_dendrariy_description">
        Dendrarium or Arboretum is a beautiful park with a large collection of over 1800 species of tropical plants, trees and shrubs.
        An extensive botanical collection of Sochi Arboretum includes species from 106 families, 310 genera of plants.
        Among most noticeable are giant eucalyptus trees, palm trees, Japanese cherry tree, yuccas, giant agave and many others.
        Mild Mediterranean climate of Sochi allowed exotic plats to flourish in the park and around the city.
        Most of these plants were brought to Sochi by famous Russian scientists Sergey Nikolayevich Khudyakov.
        Many plants were planted along Sochi streets. You can take a cable car to the top of the mountain and walk down the stairs.
        Beautiful Sochi park is dispersed by beautiful architectural buildings, terraces, stairs, fountains and others.
        The territory of the park is divided into two parts, the Upper Park and Lower Park dissected by Kurortny Avenue.
    </string>

    <string name="parks_potseluyevsky">Potseluyevsky Park</string>
    <string name="parks_potseluyevsky_description">
        Potseluevsky Square is a pleasant place for a quiet rest in the center of Sochi near the central registry office.
        No entertainment in this park you will not find, but there are many places for kisses:
        on the shady green alleys there are comfortable benches on which you can rest and wait for the day\'s heat.
        \nThis small square was laid in 1988 to the 150th anniversary of the founding of the city,
        in honor of the historical date in the park, the monument "Stone Anchor" was erected.
    </string>

    <string name="parks_ornithological">Ornithological Park</string>
    <string name="parks_ornithological_description">
        The natural ornithological park in the Imereti Valley was established after completion of large-scale Olympic construction
        in place of the bogs and lakes, used by migrating birds for a stopover. Today, the almost 300-hectare park is divided
        into 14 clusters, and is known for both its nature conservation and educational efforts.
        The park is unique as it’s the only place in Russia with preserved Colchian-type swamps inhabited by many rare plants and animals.
        Despite its residential surroundings, the birds have all the comforts here. The promenades are set up far from the bird rest spots,
        and some of the especially important ponds are fenced off, so that the visitors don’t disturb the park’s residents.
        This helps to preserve the migrating birds’ habitual stops and to increase their population, as the scientists regularly note appearance of progeny.
        At the park, you can see swans and geese, herons and diving ducks, peregrin falcons and kestrels, along with many others.
        The lakes are inhibited by turtles and snakes.
    </string>

    <string name="parks_komsomolskiy">Komsomolskiy Park</string>
    <string name="parks_komsomolskiy_description">
        This small, cosy park was planted on the left bank of the River Sochi in 1970 by a group of youth activists,
        led by young architect Valentin Kirichenko. Hence its name: Komsomolsky.
        \nThe fountain remained the park’s centrepiece for years, but more landmarks have since been added,
        including the memorial for Sochi-born soldiers who fought in the Great Patriotic War,
        and the monuments commemorating Afghan War veterans and Chernobyl Nuclear Power Plant emergency rescue workers.
        \nThis park with its green glades in the shade of the evergreen trees, its shrubberies in bloom and neat benches is one of the
        favourite recreation grounds for locals and visitors alike.
    </string>

    <string name="parks_russia_japan">Russia-Japan Friendship Garden</string>
    <string name="parks_russia_japan_description">
        Across the street from Arts Square there is a small exotic garden with a bronze dragon guarding the entrance.
        \nThis green oasis in the resort heart of Sochi was crated thirty years ago by the famous landscape architect, Sergey Venchagov.
        He planted this veritable oriental garden with glades and narrow paved paths on a tiny piece of land,
        squeezed in between Kurortny Prospekt and private homesteads. It is home to coniferous and deciduous trees,
        which are common to Japan and Russia. A weeping willow broods over a pond in the middle of the garden,
        surrounded by Korean silver firs, Japanese larches, cedars and several kinds of pine. There are no benches in this garden.
        It is customary to just walk quietly here, following the paths, contemplating the beauty.
    </string>

    <string name="parks_sochi_park">Sochi Park </string>
    <string name="parks_sochi_park_description">
        The first theme park in Russia – Sochi Park or the Russian Disneyland was open in a picturesque Imeretinskaya Lowland,
        close to the Olympic Park in the summer of 2014. The Park enjoys excellent transport accessibility.
        It\'s a very special place where little ones can meet their favorite characters from Russian folklore and
        Alexander Pushkin\'s tales and parents and grandparents can take part in many attractions specially built for Sochi Park.
        \nThere are roller coasters, thrill rides for the daring family members, kiddie rides for the children and family rides
        for everyone in the family to enjoy. Along with all of the fun rides are shows, parades, and games. And when your start to get hungry,
        you can take advantage of numerous food locations throughout the Park which includes cafes and restaurants, fun foods and meals for kids.
    </string>


    <!-- Strings for Museums and Sightseeings-->

    <string name="museums_tea_plantation">Tea Houses</string>
    <string name="museums_tea_plantation_description">
        Tea Houses is a sprawling excursion site, devoted to Sochi’s tea-growing industry,
        consisting of several log-houses and a tea plantation on a hillside.
        In the 1970s, this was the tea industry “showcase” designed to impress visiting foreign dignitaries.
        \nThe main log-house of the complex, built by Huzul craftsmen, is decorated with carved ornaments and folk artefacts,
        created by eminent Russian craftsmen. When you have learned about the history of what is probably the world’s northernmost tea,
        you can take a stroll amid the tea plantations and harvest some tealeaves to take home.
        \nAt the end of the excursion everyone sits down around a samovar to have some tea, fresh-baked pies, jam made from local fruits,
        and locally harvested honey and hazelnuts. The best time to visit is between May and October, when tea is harvested.
        The plantation offers a breathtaking view of the Caucasus Mountains.
    </string>

    <string name="museums_akhun_tower">The Observation Tower on Akhun Mountain</string>
    <string name="museums_akhun_tower_description">
        On the way to Matsesta, there is a viewing platform offering an astonishing panoramic view of Greater Sochi.
        In clear weather, even the Turkish coast is visible from here.
        The platform is located on the tower constructed at the peak of Akhun Mountain, which rises 663 metres above sea level.
    </string>

    <string name="museums_singing_fontains">The Singing Fontains</string>
    <string name="museums_singing_fontains_description">
        In the center of the Olympic Park is the Medals Plaza. Its main attractions are the singing fountain and the Olympic torch pylon.
        During 2014 Winter Games, thousands of fans gathered here to honour the winners, and there were musical performances every night.
        The plaza is round like a medal, with a triangular pattern of lawns around the perimeter. To this day,
        it remains a magnet for thousands of tourists.
        The plaza offers a great view of all the Olympic arenas and Fisht Stadium that will host 2018 FIFA World Cup.
        It is still used for concerts and performances, and a special stage is erected on such nights.
        \nIn the evenings, the amazing Olympic Fire Chalice singing fountain performs hour-long light-and-music shows to the accompaniment
        of classical music and contemporary hits. Every night, hundreds of visitors come to watch the show.
    </string>

    <string name="museums_svyato_troitsky_temple">Svyato-Troitsky Church</string>
    <string name="museums_svyato_troitsky_temple_description">
        The Svyato-Troitsky Church was built and consecrated on May 31, 1998 in the territory where
        the Temple of the Descent of the Holy Spirit was earlier from 1898 to 1947. This territory is a historically memorable place
        for the laying of Fort Adler (1837) and a protected historical and landscape area where the settlement of Adler was founded.
    </string>

    <string name="museums_auto_sport_museum">Sochi Auto Sport Museum</string>
    <string name="museums_auto_sport_museum_description">
        The museum features around 50 racing and sports cars, including a genuine Jaguar R5B Formula 1 car,
        a 1,500-horsepower Dodge Viper for drag racing, a Jaguar XJ220, which held the speed record in the 1990s, a legendary Ferrari F40,
        the race car for public roads, a Formula RUS racing car, and a Soviet Pobeda Sport car from way back in the 1950s.
        The museum has several thousand exhibits, including model cars, a collection of caps and watches, driver and mechanic outfits,
        a Formula 1 photo gallery, books, photographs, magazines, a unique display of all Pirelli calendars from 1964 to 2018, and a
        fantastic gallery of paintings by Russian, Ukrainian, and Kazakh artists. There is a souvenir shop in the museum.
    </string>

    <string name="museums_stalin_residence">Stalin\'s Summer Residence</string>
    <string name="museums_stalin_residence_description">
        At Stalin\'s Summer Residence (Museum Of USSR History), sit on the dictator\'s couch, and touch his leather jacket
        and other personal belongings. Painted green for camouflage, the house on top of the ridge is surrounded by palms and cedars.
        Inside the dark interior, you\'ll see heavy curtains, redwood furniture, a pool 1.52 m (5 ft) deep, and a small army cot.
        A wax figure of Stalin sits in his study. According to rumor, Stalin haunts the house.
        The complex features a hotel and a restaurant where you can sample homemade eastern dishes.
    </string>

    <string name="museums_art_museum">Sochi Art Museum</string>
    <string name="museums_art_museum_description">
        On display at Sochi’s Art Museum is a collection of 19th- and 20th-century Russian paintings and graphic art:
        landscapes and seascapes by Ivan Shishkin and Ivan Aivazovsky, still-lifes by Pyotr Konchalovsky and Ilya Mashkov,
        drawings by Valentin Serov, Boris Kustodiev and Aleksander Deineka. But the pride of place at the museum belongs
        to the Mzymta Treasure – a large cache of iron, bronze, silver and gold artefacts of Sarmat and ancient Greek origin,
        unearthed by the River Mzymta in 1997.
    </string>

    <string name="museums_marine_station">Marine Station</string>
    <string name="museums_marine_station_description">
        Sochi’s sea-gate is 1.5 kilometres away from the railway station. The sea terminal, which is on the official architectural landmarks list,
        looks like a real palace. The former Marina, now a shopping and amusement centre,
        was built in the mid-20th century to the design of Karo Alabian and Leonid Karlik. With its majestic colonnade, open terraces,
        broad stairways and arches, and its 70-metre tower with a steeple, it is quite reminiscent of St. Petersburg’s Admiralty.
        The central tower is adorned with a sculptural composition: the female statues represent seasons of the year,
        the male statues stand for the cardinal points, and the dolphins symbolize the opulence of the Black Sea coast.
        Following a massive rebuilding and the addition of some new buildings on the northern pier, Sochi’s passenger port is now the largest
        in the Black Sea region. It remains open for supersize ships all year round. Global cruise expos and regattas take place here on a regular basis.
        \nThere are two noteworthy monuments next to the port. The one in the park across from the rotunda commemorates Peter I,
        the emperor who expanded Russia so that it gained access to the three seas: Baltic, Azov and Black. He did not, however,
        build any navy on the Black Sea, like he did on the Baltic Sea. The second monument,
        standing in the shade of some sycamores by the southern pier, depicts the seeing-off of the main characters of Soviet cult
        comedy Diamond Arm on their overseas cruise. That scene was actually filmed at the Sochi port.
    </string>

    <string name="museums_train_station">Train Station Sochi</string>
    <string name="museums_train_station_description">
        The building of the railway station was designed by Alexey Dushkin. Its construction was started on 13 September 1950
        and completed on 10 September 1952, and the luggage section was added in 1956.
        In the 1950s Sochi played an important role in the Soviet Unions, being a major transit point from Russia to Georgia
        and the most popular health resort for a large number of ordinary citizens and Communist Party leaders, including Joseph Stalin.
        Consequently, the station construction was curated by an unusually large number of ministries, and by Stalin himself.
        While Dushkin's design was considered elegant by many curators, including Stalin, it was criticised by others for excessive costs.
        Dushkin built a twin version of the Sochi station in Simferopol in 1951. In 1975, the Sochi station was included to the Russian
        list of architectural monuments of federal importance.
    </string>

    <string name="museums_matsesta">Matsesta Kurort</string>
    <string name="museums_matsesta_description">
        Matsesta, meaning \'fire water\', has harnessed the powers of the hot sulphur springs that have become synonymous
        with Sochi and become the city\'s most renowned health spa. The water contains over 27 types of minerals and is used
        to treat people with respiratory and cardiac problems. Featuring a number of bathing rooms, massage tables and inhalation cubicles,
        Matsesta Spa is a major tourist attraction.
    </string>

    <string name="museums_of_sochi">Museum of the Resort Town of Sochi</string>
    <string name="museums_of_sochi_description">
        The Museum of History of the Resort City of Sochi houses the main treasures of this area.
        It was founded with a collection established at the beginning of the twentieth century by the Caucasus Mountain Club:
        minerals found in the mountains, herbariums of local plants, artefacts from the homes of the native coastal peoples.
        The collection has expanded and now provides an idea of the entire history of the Russian South.
        \nIn the museum’s courtyard is an historical dolmen tomb from Lazarevskoye Village.
        As you move through the halls, the pages of Sochi’s history unfold one by one. One hall features Bronze Age tools,
        arrows and clay bowls. Another contains a ship filled with Turkish yatagan knives and Cossack sabres.
        Elsewhere, the museum includes a diorama featuring bears, mountain goats and black cockerels;
        miniature replicas of ancient summer houses; a collection of weaponry used by the soldiers of the White Guards and the Red Army;
        and phonographs and tableware from the first Soviet resorts. The Soyuz-9 space module,
        in which Andriyan Nikolayev and Vitaly Sevastyanov returned from space and underwent rehabilitation in Sochi in 1970, is also here.
        Their 17-day journey was the longest space trip ever made at that time.
    </string>

    <!--Strings for Restaurants and Cafe -->

    <string name="cafe_delmar">DelMar</string>
    <string name="cafe_delmar_description">
        Del Mar is a café on the waterfront with lots of fish and seafood on the menu: soup DelMar di mare, tuna tartar,
        cream stewed mussels, shrimp tempura, Genoa salad. The seafood offering fits in well with Italian food: delicious thin-crust pizza,
        Parma ham pasta… Even Japanese selections are served with Italian flair at Del Mar: the sushi rolls have names like Liguria
        or Calabria. Wash it all down with any of the numerous French, Argentinean and Chilean wines on offer.
        \nWhen it’s warm out, most people sit out on the porch or at the tables down by the water’s edge.
        A visit to Del Mar in the morning is a special kind of pleasure. That’s when they serve Italian omelette,
        syrniki  and house breakfast. The kids get their own menu with titles like ABC chicken soup,
        mini burger and franks with mashed potatoes.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_chaika">Chaika</string>
    <string name="cafe_chaika_description">
        Located in the historic Sochi Seaport terminal building, this upscale eatery serves European and Russian dishes.
        Specialties include a variety of grilled local fish, risottos, and pastas, plus candy and ice-cream made on the premises.
        Take in the seaport views on the outdoor veranda during warmer months and watch boats arrive and depart.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_brigantina">Brigantina</string>
    <string name="cafe_brigantina_description">
        Brigantina is a French restaurant in Sochi’s old port neighbourhood.
        This is where people come for fresh fish and seafood, both local and imported: oysters, snails, mussels, crab, scallops, clams,
        shrimp, and many kinds of Black Sea fishes: mackerel, surmullet, and all the rest of the local catch. They also make pizza here,
        which is available for takeout. The prices are not exactly low: a pot of mussels will set you back 950 rubles.
        But the view of the sea and the port is fabulous. Sit out on the porch, sipping French or Italian wine, watching the sunset,
        the sailboats and the big ships at anchorage off in the distance.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_cho_kharcho">Che? Kharcho!</string>
    <string name="cafe_cho_kharcho_description">
        Che? Kharcho! is a café launched by the Moscow restaurant group White Rabbit Family,
        whose restaurant White Rabbit is ranked 18 on The World’s 50 Best Restaurants 2016.
        \nIn two cafes Che? Kharcho! offers Black Sea food in the broadest possible sense, with an emphasis on grilled selections.
        Their concept of “Black Sea food” evidently includes everything we’ve been accustomed, since childhood,
        to eating when on seaside holiday in the South: khinkali, shish kebab, satsivi, chicken rissoles, kharcho, lulah kebab and local fish,
        both freshwater and saltwater. The owners of Che? Kharcho! claim and continually reiterate that all their food is prepared
        from local produce. The menu lists some complicated lemonades, berry drinks and compotes. The bar menu is not so diverse,
        but Georgian and Crimean wines are on.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_khmeli_suneli">Khmeli and Suneli</string>
    <string name="cafe_khmeli_suneli_description">
        Although this Georgian restaurant also has Italian specialties and things like borsch, Caesar salad and the Russian classic –
        Olivier salad on the menu, most patrons come to Khmeli and Suneli for its Georgian food. This restaurant is hard to miss.
        It’s right in the centre of Sochi, it has a large, comfortable porch, and the enticing smells of char-broiled meat emanating
        from it will guide you right to it. Their scrumptious veal shawarma is legendary. Very few restaurants get Tarkhun tarragon
        lemonade right, as in ‘not too sticky-sweet’. Khmeli and Suneli pulls it off: their Tarkhun has a fresh and subtle taste.
        \nThe restaurant runs a deli outlet: you can take your favourite food home with you. They serve breakfast in the morning,
        which is worth getting up early for. Make sure you order the Adzharian khachapuri scaled down to toy size for your child.
        After dinner, you can send your kid off to cooking master-class, which the restaurant offers on a regular basis.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_lighthouse">LightHouse</string>
    <string name="cafe_lighthouse_description">
        Restaurant Lighthouse is the best panoramic place in Sochi. It is located on the 7th and 8th floor near the residential complex
        Lighthouse of Alexandria. Included in the top 10 best panoramic restaurants in the south of Russia.
        The restaurant is in 2-minute walk from the pebble beach of the Black Sea and 5 minutes from the Festival concert hall.
        Enjoy the meal, try the delicious dishes that are cooked with love. Decent service, stable quality.
        A large selection of fine wines. The music in Lounge style, and not only that… Free parking for our dear guests.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_vostochnyy_kvartal">Vostochnyy Kvartal</string>
    <string name="cafe_vostochnyy_kvartal_description">
        Vostochnyy Kvartal is a real oasis of eastern culture on the Black Sea coast.
        It is built and painted in the best traditions of national architecture by masters and artists from Uzbekistan.
        \nGuests will be able to appreciate Uzbek cuisine: real Chaikhan pilaf, samsa and tortillas from tandyr, lagman and santa,
        sazan-kabob and shish kebabs. The Vostochnyy Kvartal is located near the sea, and the windows offer a wonderful view of the sea.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_baran_rapan">Baran-Rapan</string>
    <string name="cafe_baran_rapan_description">
        The size of this huge two-storey restaurant is matched by the size of its bulging menu, prevalently Georgian and Mediterranean
        with lots of fish and seafood. They have everything a seaside holiday-maker can dream of. The interior design of Baran-Rapan
        is elaborate, thought-through down to the tiniest detail.
        \nMost patrons come to Baran-Rapan for its extensive seafood selection which is, indeed, impressive.
        But this restaurant is also notable for its elegant service, which often turns a regular dinner into a festive experience.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_fettuchchine">Fettuchchine</string>
    <string name="cafe_fettuchchine_description">
        Trattoria Fettuccine – is an Italian restaurant for the whole family, where we honor traditions,
        whether it be recipes of grandmother or creative cuisine by Chef Daniele Benedetti of Italy!
        \nThe trattoria reign authentic Italian food products: pasta of Italian fresco meal \"semola\", entirely handmade,
        pizza on a thin flat shortcake from the authentic Italian wood-burning oven and homemade limoncello.
        \nIn addition to the simple and clear, but the delicious taste of Italian dishes in a trattoria can find a souvenir shop and
        Italian products. Democratic approach does not leave anyone indifferent, because the combination of high-quality service,
        authentic Italian cuisine and affordable prices – a truly rare.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_corks_wine">CORKs Wine Bar and Kitchen</string>
    <string name="cafe_corks_wine_description">
        The atmospheric loft-style interior with rarity brickwork, a cozy terrace that works even in winter, an unusual wine list and
        a very modern cuisine are all CORKs. Restaurant\'s menu is designed so that each dish reveals the taste of wine.
        And the main thing to try here is something from section \"Fingerfood\" - light snacks like pate, tartar or bruschetta.
        For those who prefers more serious meals we recommend home burrata, tomato soup with cod and steaks. All with wine, for sure.
    </string>

    <!-- Strings for Nature Attractions -->

    <string name="nature_agura_waterfalls">Agura Waterfalls </string>
    <string name="nature_agura_waterfalls_description">
        Agura Waterfallls is one of the innumerable waterfalls in Sochi. One of the famous tourist attractions in Sochi,
        the picturesque location of Agura Waterfalls draws a lot of travelers from all across the world.
        Also known as Agursky, this waterfalls is one of the most frequented places of sightseeing in Sochi.
        The locale of Agura Waterfalls, Sochi is a popular hiking trail in the area.
        \nCascading from a height of 30 meters, the Agura Waterfalls in Sochi meanders through the ledges, dividing into separate rivulets.
    </string>

    <string name="nature_33_waterfalls">33 Waterfalls </string>
    <string name="nature_33_waterfalls_description">
        The grand cascade of 33 falls is located on the River Shakhe in the Lazarevsky District.
        It’s easier to get here with a tour group or an offroading party. The road traverses a mountain village and follows a riverbed.
        This well-known cascade of relatively small falls, slides and rapids – the tallest one is about 7 metres – is on the right-hand
        tributary of the Shakhe, the Jegosh, which is less than two kilometres long, including the non-perennial section of its riverbed.
        There are some cafés and gift outlets at the beginning of the route. The wooden bridges and stairs on both banks of the river
        take you to 17 out of 33 falls. Those wishing to see more will have to make their own way through the forest and along
        the rocky banks. The whole route runs through shady woodland. Part of the appeal of these waterfalls are the lakes they form,
        in which people are wont to swim.
    </string>

    <string name="nature_mamedovo_canyon">Mamedovo Gorge</string>
    <string name="nature_mamedovo_canyon_description">
        This part of the Sochi National Park in the valley of the River Kuapse, squeezed, as it were, between two mountain ranges –
        Asheisky and Bezymyanny – is overgrown with oaks, chestnuts, beeches and ferns.
        \nThe gorge is named after Old Man Mahmed, the hero of local lore. Like Ivan Susanin of Russia, Mahmed,
        hired as a local guide by enemy soldiers, led them into the neck of woods where they died, and thus saved his village.
        \nThe entrance to the gorge is impeded by a heap of rocks from a rock-fall, beyond which the prepared trail begins.
        If you follow it, you will pass a little grotto and enter a narrow rocky corridor. The river, which toiled to carve itself a
        passage to the sea, built a veritable arch here. Three metres up, the walls of the gorge converge. Beyond the tunnel the gorge
        expands abruptly. This is what the locals call the White Hall, due to all the chalk-stone washed up on the bank at the river-bend.
        The water falling down one of the walls of the \"Hall\" from a height of more than 10 metres is called Mahmed\’s Beard.
        Another waterfall nearby has formed a semblance of a basin, which they call Mahmed’s Bathtub. Still farther down the gorge
        you will discover a cascade of three bathing bowls, which the locals call the bowls of health, beauty and love.
        At this point the trail climbs up, bringing the traveller back to the walnut glade.
    </string>

    <string name="nature_yew_and_boxtree">Yew and boxtree wood</string>
    <string name="nature_yew_and_boxtree_description">
        The yew and box-tree grove is a unique old-growth forest in the Khosta District of Sochi, which has existed since before Ice Age,
        miraculously surviving both major construction projects and great natural calamities.
        Even though it has seen some major damage from the boxwood fungus in the past two years, the grove is still spell-bindingly beautiful.
        \nSpecially appointed pathways lead the tourists through the thickets, precipitous rocks and stone labyrinths past the ruins
        of an 11th/12th-century fortress and some caves, dead-ending at a turbulent mountain stream. The sprawling tops of the mighty,
        ages-old yews keep most of the grove in the cool shade even on a scorching summer day.
        \nThere are two excursion routes one can follow, two and five kilometres long. On the way,
        you can rest in the secluded arbours or on benches. The sign-posts will inform you of the local florae and faunae,
        as well as the directions.
    </string>

    <string name="nature_krasnaya_polyana">Krasnaya Polyana Mountain Cluster</string>
    <string name="nature_krasnaya_polyana_description">
        Krasnaya Polyana features mountains, waterfalls, ancient dolmen tombs, ravines and mineral water sources.
        It also has three mountain ski resorts: Roza Khutor, Laura and Gornaya Karusel, which are the best of their kind in Europe today.
        Chalets, restaurants, shops, clubs and children’s playgrounds are connected by paths and rope ways. In the summer,
        when there is no snow, the cycling season opens in the resorts.
    </string>

    <string name="nature_eagle_rock">Orlinye Skaly</string>
    <string name="nature_eagle_rock_description">
        From the Agura River, a trail leads to the other local landmark, Orlinye Skaly, overhanging the gorge.
        The view that opens up on the mountains, the sea, the dark woods and the river from the top of Orlinye Skaly takes your breath away.
        The elation is further enhanced by the statue of Prometheus erected on the rocks. Legend has it that the rock to which the
        Olympian Gods chained Prometheus in punishment for stealing fire from the Gods and giving it to humans, was right here.
    </string>

    <string name="nature_devils_gate_canyon">Chertovy Vorota Canyon</string>
    <string name="nature_devils_gate_canyon_description">
        This natural treasure, protected by the state, is located in the valley of the River Khosta. C
        hertovy Vorota, or \"Devil\’s Gate\", is a small canyon of amazing beauty close to the confluence of the West and East Khosta.
        Water had to work for thousands upon thousands of years to carve it in the rocks, so that today we stand spell-bound
        by the smooth undulations of the 50-metre rock faces, and the sandbars and smooth bottom of the canyon,
        which is only five metres across at the widest. The curves are what gave this canyon its name.
        Chertovy Vorota is surrounded by primal forest, where plants from before the Ice Age occur. This nature sanctuary is of two parts:
        one is open to the public, the other is restricted. You can walk through the yew and box-tree grove to reach Chertovy Vorota,
        or you can drive and park by the picnic ground with tables and fire pits. There is also a small beach on the bank of the mountain
        river nearby.
    </string>

    <string name="nature_vorontsovska_caves">Vorontsovka Caves</string>
    <string name="nature_vorontsovska_caves_description">
        One of the longest surrender buildings anyplace in Russia, the Vorontsovka Caves contain confirmation of human home going back
        a mind boggling 20,000 years. It is this reality, alongside the holes\' striking visual appearance,
        that draws guests here from great distances abroad. Situated in the Khosta and Adler regions of Sochi,
        the holes can be explored by foot through a progression of doorways spotting the inclines of the Kudepsta River Valley at statures
        of up to 720 meters above ocean level. There's photograph openings wherever you look, so make certain to bring your camera,
        and durable footwear is additionally unequivocally prescribed.
    </string>

    <string name="nature_akhtyrshskaya_cave">Akhtyrshskaya Cave</string>
    <string name="nature_akhtyrshskaya_cave_description">
        Famous for its picturesque views and underground lakes, Akhtyrshskaya Cave encapsulates within itself primeval remains
        and petroglyphic drawings. On your visit, you’ll observe ruins of the former watchtower accompanied with some wonderful waterfalls.
        It’s interesting to learn that the southern exit if the cave is located approximately 100m above the river.
        Those of you who are interested in photography can test their skills by capturing some real nice panoramic views and beautiful
        sceneries surrounding the cave.
    </string>

    <!-- Strings for Entertainments -->

    <string name="entertainments_yacht_club">Yacht club Sochi</string>
    <string name="entertainments_yacht_club_description">
        Yacht club \"Sochi\" is located in the center of the resort city, on the left bank of the river Bzugu.
        \nThe complex of buildings and structures was commissioned on the eve of the Moscow Olympics in 1980,
        as a base for the preparation of the Russian national sailing team.\nThe capacity of the water area of ​​the yacht port
        is up to 60 boats and yachts of various classes. Depths in the harbor - from 2 to 3 metres;
        the width of the entrance channel is 30 metres, the depth is 2.8 metres. Marina is protected by hydraulic structures -
        concrete South and North mole. The length of berthing facilities is 330 m. There is a bunkering station;
        repair shops for boats, slipways.
    </string>

    <string name="entertainments_malibu_club">Malibu Night Club</string>
    <string name="entertainments_malibu_club_description">
        This is the largest and most popular night resort of the Black Sea coast.\nThe area of Malibu is about 1500 square meters,
        which makes it possible to comfortably accommodate about 1000 guests. The club is a two-level open area,
        where there are 4 cocktail bars, a soft zone, a Japanese zone, a VIP-box and full parking. The tropical design of the building
        is successfully combined with the beauty of the sea coast, the noise of the surf and the unique aroma of unique plants
        in the park zone.\nThe club offers a variety of concert programs, shows, themed parties, performances of famous
        DJs and corporate events. Here is the annual tango forum, in which world stars take part.
        \nA distinctive feature of Malibu is the constant change of design.
    </string>

    <string name="entertainments_winter_theater">The Winter Theatre</string>
    <string name="entertainments_winter_theater_description">
        The Winter Theatre (Zimny Teatr) was built in 1937, and quickly became one of its key landmarks.
        The building itself is a sight to behold. It has become one of Russia\'s architectural monuments.
        Designed by Konstantin Chernopyatov, the icredibly \'light\' structure rests upon 88 columns, running around the building\'s
        perimeter. The front of the theatre is adorned with three goddesses, as if they have graced it personally by descending to
        the mortal realm from Olympus: Melpomene, Terpsichore and Talia. Famous Russian sculptor Vera Mukhina authored these statues.
    </string>

    <string name="entertainments_organ_hall">Organ and Chamber Music Hall</string>
    <string name="entertainments_organ_hall_description">
        Hall of Organ and Chamber Music named after Alice Debolskaya was erected in mid 1960s. Designed by Evgeniy Serdyukov,
        the building barely changed its exterior throughout half a century. It still has the original mosaic on its front,
        as well as the garden with exotic plants. The Organ was provided by the Rieger-Kloss company in 1986. It\'s quite impressive
        with 2,500 pipes. The first concert here was played by the famous Garry Grodberg.
        \nThe unique acoustics of the hall, suited for just 340 visitors, allow a wide variety of concerts,
        from organ to choir and symphonic. It\'s considered to be the main academic music venue in Sochi.
    </string>

    <string name="entertainments_festivalniy">Festival Concert Hall</string>
    <string name="entertainments_festivalniy_description">
        One of the largest concert venues in Russia and the most famous concert hall in Sochi. The schedule of the Concert Hall
        has been always very tight and many popular stars come here several times during the summer season.
        Most performers are Russian pop singers. This is also a venue for various festivals and competitions.
        The hall capacity is 2500 people. Not all the seats allow good view, so it is better to get a place far from the stage
        but in the middle. Tickets cost 1000-5000 rubles depending on the concert. A small drawback: as the hall is open you can hear
        sounds from the street.
    </string>

    <string name="entertainments_treugolnik">Treugolnik Rock-Bar</string>
    <string name="entertainments_treugolnik_description">
        A legendary place that has recently celebrated its 20-year anniversary. It often hosts popular rock-groups
        (the ticket price is 1000-1500 roubles) and almost every evening there are performances of young teams
        (entrance is free or up to 300 roubles). Here you will see a lot of somewhat gloomy regular customers dressed in leather
        and jeans clothes, and brick walls and dark wood add Brutalism to the interior. The prices for beer and snacks are a bit
        overestimated, but the atmosphere is great. The place is located away from the center – in the Adler district of Sochi.
    </string>

    <string name="entertainments_horses">Horse riding</string>
    <string name="entertainments_horses_description">
        One of the most favourite amusement for tourists in the Greater Sochi. As a rule, the rides start from remote districts
        of the city agglomeration – Dagomys, Akhun or Hosta but sometimes you can find rides from Adler too.
        They last from one or two hours (500-1200 roubles) for 7-8 hours (from 3000-4000 roubles) and can be organized around picturesque
        suburbs (in the fields or along the sea coast) or with visits to some natural attractions like canyons and waterfalls.
        There are also several day riding tours.
    </string>

    <string name="entertainments_rafting">Rafting</string>
    <string name="entertainments_rafting_description">
        Sochi offers great opportunities for those who like extreme tourism: the local mountain rivers suit both for the novices
        and for experienced rafters. As a rule, most raft-tours take place in the area of Krasnaya Polyana on the Mzymta River,
        but other options are available too.
        \nThe price for rafting per person is not very high: from 500 to 1000 roubles per 1-3 hours.
        However, you should honestly assess your capacity in order not to get into trouble.
    </string>

    <string name="entertainments_skypark">Skypark AJ Hackett Sochi</string>
    <string name="entertainments_skypark_description">
        The only in Russia park for extreme entertainment on a high altitude was founded in Sochi in 2014 and became one of the main
        sights of the city. It was created by a New Zealand traveler and extreme sportsman Alan Hacket,
        who created similar parks in Australia, Germany, France, Singapour and China.
        Thousands of tourists come to the park to walk on a walking bridge 439 meters long, which was built over the Akhshtyskoye canyon.
        From the altitude of 207 meters a great view opens to the valley of Mzyma river and the Caucasus mountains.
        The most desperate people decide to have the highest budju jump from the bridge – from an altitude of 69 or 207 meters.
        Those, who are not ready for such jumps, can swing on the highest swings in the world and ride a megatroll
        with the speed of 150 km/h. In the Sky park there is a rope park, a climbing wall, via ferrata on the cliff area of the canyon,
        a budju-jump museum and an Amphitheatre.
    </string>

    <string name="entertainments_galaktika">Galaktika social and cultural centre</string>
    <string name="entertainments_galaktika_description">
        The social and cultural centre Galaktika is part of the mountain and tourist centre Gazprom, which is located at the altitude
        of 540 meters above the sea level. Up to four thousand guests may stay there simultaneously.
        The cosmic world of Galaktika creates an unusual design of the centre, which takes you at times to open space and at times
        to some sections of a space ship. All year round there is an aquapark with a unique open heated pool and with a view
        to the mountain peaks. The fans of winter entertainment may go figure skating on an all-year-round ice arena.
        The spirit of competition reigns in the bowling centre and the billiard club. There are also three cinema centres in Galaktika,
        a children’s development club and a night club, a food court and some restaurants. There are parking places for 1200 cars.
    </string>

    <string name="entertainments_mayak">Cabaret Mayak</string>
    <string name="entertainments_mayak_description">
        Perhaps Russia\'s most famous gay club, thanks to the massive media attention received during the 2014 Sochi Olympics,
        Cabaret Mayak is now in a new location near the train station. Inside, drag queens and other performers continue to strut their stuff.
        Face control keeps out the uncool, so make sure you look your best.
    </string>

</resources>
